

Kostadin Karaivanov

Web developer

An experienced with programming skills and over 16 years of experience in IT technologies i deliver an immersive user experience through create responsive websites that are fast, easy to use, and built with best practices. My approach is to create an app design that strengthens your face's/company's brand while ensuring ease of use and simplicity for your audience.

\times	kostadin.karaivanov@outlook.com		+359 889 212114
0	Panagyurishte, Bulgaria		karaivanov.eu
in	linkedin.com/in/kostadin-karaivanov-8390061a5	0	github.com/kkaraivanov

WORK EXPERIENCE

Computer systems technician

Asarel-Medet JSC

10/2006 - 09/2017

- Computer support
- Software support of users
- Network support technician
- Troubleshooting software and hardware problems

System administrator Asarel-Medet JSC

01/2018 - 08/2019

- Developed information security policy
- Participation in a project for implementation of GDPR
- Contributed to integrating DLP security system
- Administration of over 700 devices in the active directory
- Database administration of the SAP system
- Support of the VMware, Exchange server, Mail and Web IronPort firewall systems

Specialist

Asarel-Medet JSC

10/2019 - 06/2022

Panagyurishte, Bulgaria

Panagyurishte, Bulgaria

Panagyurishte, Bulgaria

- Data processing from water level data loggers
- Data processing from gps prisms to monitor the change of land masses

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Tour Posrtal 2

- Is my defense project for ASP.NET Core course at SoftUni (June-August 2021).
- This is a site that represents a platform for gathering people looking for a hotel to visit and hoteliers offering their services. The main idea is to organize a space in which businesses can get a working environment, offering and selling their services, and consumers having easy access to them.

CSICorpMobile

- Conceptual design of a software solution for data collection and review from an automated system for measuring air quality in an open pit mine

EDUCATION

C# Full-Stack Developer Software University

09/2019 - Present.

- ➤ C# OOP
- ➤ C# Web 🛂
- C# Masterclass
- ➤ ASP.NET Core ☑
- Entity Framework Core
- SQL, MSSQL, MvSQL
- JS Advanced
- JS Applications
- WordPress Essentials
- WordPress Developers 2
- **QA Fundamentals Core**
- Data Structures

TECHNICAL SKILLS

T.	1	1	I
ASP.NET/	ASP.NET Core		
)
Entity Fra	mework/Entity F	ramework Core)
Xamarin			
React			
Bootstrap)		

CLOUD SERVICE SKILLS

1	1	1	
Azure			
Azure DevOps			
Github			

LANGUAGES KNOWLEDGE

JavaScript \odot \odot \bigcirc \bigcirc HTMI \odot \odot \odot \odot CSS \odot \odot \odot \odot

INTERESTS

